BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White, Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Personal Papers, 1936-1977, undated; 3
  This series contains seven subseries: I. Datebooks, II. Literary Productions, III. Lessons and Notes, IV. Sunday School Lessons, V. Family Illness and Funerals, VI. Awards, and VII. Subject Files. The Datebook subseries contains White's journals and appointment books and is arranged chronologically. The Literary Productions subseries is the published and unpublished material from White's speeches, books, articles, and sermons. This subseries is arranged alphabetically. White wrote Sunday school lessons for the Sunday School Board based in Nashville, Tennessee beginning in 1962 until his death in 1977. The Sunday School Lessons subseries is arranged chronologically. Family Illness and Funerals document the declining health of Edna and Catherine. It also contains a sampling of condolences from the funerals of White and his wives. This series is arranged chronologically. Awards include the various plaques and certificates given in honor of the Whites throughout their lifetime. This series is arranged alphabetically. Subject Files are folders that cover various issues and topics. They have been arranged alphabetically.
  - Datebook, 1948-1976; 1
    - Desk Book, 1948 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Datebook, 1949 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Diary, 1953 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Diary, 1954 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Datebook, 1959 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Datebook, 1960 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Calendar, 1960 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Datebook, 1961 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Academic Diary, 1961-1962 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Datebook, 1962 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Datebook, 1963 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Datebook, 1964 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Datebook, 1965 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Datebook, 1966 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Datebook, 1968 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Datebook, 1969 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Datebook, 1972 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Datebook, 1974 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Minder, 1976 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - undated Journal (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Literary Productions, 1938-1976, undated; 2
    - "A Baptist Manifesto" (1 of 3), undated (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - "A Baptist Manifesto" (2 of 3), undated (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - "A Baptist Manifesto" (3 of 3), undated (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - "A Baptist Manifesto" Final Print (1 of 3), undated (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - "A Baptist Manifest" Final Print (2 of 3), undated (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - "A Baptist Manifesto" Final Print (3 of 3), undated (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - "A Contrast in Wisdom-Communist Ideology vs. Christian Concepts", 1965 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - "A Dangerous Revolt", 1964 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - "A Determined Step Forward Now or Miss the Bus", undated (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - "A New Strategy in a New Age", 1965 (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - "A New Strategy in a New Age", undated (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - "A Sickening Soggy Sag" (unfinished), undated (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - "Are Our Schools Fulfilling Their Mission to the Denomination", undated (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - "A Section of the Story of W.R. White’s Life" (1 of 2), undated (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - "A Section of the Story of W.R. White's Life" (2 of 2), undated (Box 193, Folder 16)
    - "A World-Wide Revival for Survival", undated (Box 193, Folder 17)
    - Address to San Marcos Graduates, 1971 (Box 193, Folder 18)
    - Alien Immersion-Whither?, 1965 (Box 193, Folder 19)
    - Archaeology-Wellhausens, undated (Box 193, Folder 20)
    - Articles (1 of 4), 1950-1951 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Articles (2 of 4), 1950-1951 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Articles (3 of 4), 1950-1951 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Articles (4 of 4), 1950-1951 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Articles, 1951-1952 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Articles (1 of 3), 1952 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Articles (2 of 3), 1952 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Articles (3 of 3), 1952 (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Articles (1 of 5), 1953 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Articles (2 of 5), 1953 (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Articles (3 of 5), 1953 (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Articles (4 of 5), 1953 (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Articles (5 of 5), 1953 (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Articles (1 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - Articles (2 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 194, Folder 15)
    - Articles (3 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 194, Folder 16)
    - Articles (4 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 194, Folder 17)
    - Articles (5 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Articles (6 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Articles (7 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Articles (1 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Articles (2 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Articles (3 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Articles (4 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Articles (5 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Articles (6 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Articles (7 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Articles (8 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Articles (9 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Articles (10 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Articles (11 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - Articles (12 of 12), 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - Articles (1 of 6), 1956-1957 (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - Articles (2 of 6), 1956-1957 (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Articles (3 of 6), 1956-1957 (Box 195, Folder 18)
    - Articles (4 of 6), 1956-1957 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Articles (5 of 6), 1956-1957 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Articles (6 of 6), 1956-1957 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Articles, 1957 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Articles 1 (1 of 9), undated (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Articles 1 (2 of 9), undated (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Articles 1 (3 of 9), undated (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Articles 1 (4 of 9), undated (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Articles 1 (5 of 9), undated (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Articles 1 (6 of 9), undated (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Articles 1 (7 of 9), undated (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Articles 1 (8 of 9), undated (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Articles 1 (9 of 9), undated (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - Articles 2 (1 of 7), undated (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Articles 2 (2 of 7), undated (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - Articles 2 (3 of 7), undated (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - Articles 2 (4 of 7), undated (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - Articles 2 (5 of 7), undated (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - Articles 2 (6 of 7), undated (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Articles 2 (7 of 7), undated (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Articles 3, undated (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Articles W.R. White 1, undated (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Articles W.R. White 2, undated (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Articles by Others, undated (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Article for Baptist Review, 1975 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Article in Abraham Lincoln by Carl Sandburg, undated (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - "The Authoritative Word", 1976 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - "Bankruptcy of Unbelief", undated (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - "Baptist Defectionists and Perfectionists", undated (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - "Baptist Maturing", undated (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Baptist Foundation History, 1962 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - The Baptist Review, 1951 February (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - The Baptist Review, 1961 January-February (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - The Baptist Review, 1961 September-October (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - The Baptist Review (1 of 3), 1968-1972 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - The Baptist Review (2 of 3), 1968-1972 (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - The Baptist Review (3 of 3), 1968-1972 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - The Baptist Review “Tribute to a Remarkable Woman”, 1970 September-October (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - Baptist Standard (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - Baptist Standard (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - The Baylor Line, 1958 January-February (Box 197, Folder 23)
    - Baylor Lodge and its Contributions, undated (Box 197, Folder 24)
    - "Baylor’s New Day" (published in Baylor Line), undated (Box 197, Folder 25)
    - "Beautiful Formosa", undated (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - "The Bible and Baylor", undated (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - "The Bible Proved by its Own Test", undated (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Bill Wallace and Articles by W.R. White, undated (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Biographical Information, 1969 September 12 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - "The Biblical Basis for Christian Higher Education" (1 of 4), 1963, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - "The Biblical Basis for Christian Higher Education" (2 of 4), 1963, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - "The Biblical Basis for Christian Higher Education" (3 of 4), 1963, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - "The Biblical Basis for Christian Higher Education" (4 of 4), 1963, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Biographical Material Dr. White (1 of 3), 1956-1975 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Biographical Material Dr. White (2 of 3), 1956-1975 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Biographical Material Dr. White (3 of 3), 1956-1975 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Dr. White Biography (1 of 3), 1960-1962 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Dr. White Biography (2 of 3), 1960-1962 (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Dr. White Biography (3 of 3), 1960-1962 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Boy Scout Movement and Baptist Churches and “Outreach of Scouting”, undated (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Broadway’s Best Broadcasting, undated (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - Carr P. Collins Speeches, 1962, 1964, 1967 (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - Carr P. Collins Book (1 of 3), undated (Box 198, Folder 19)
    - Carr P. Collins Book (2 of 3), undated (Box 198, Folder 20)
    - Carr P. Collins Book (3 of 3), undated (Box 198, Folder 21)
    - "Carry on with Widening Reach and Heightened Power", 1966 (Box 198, Folder 22)
    - "Carry on with Widening Reach and Heightened Power", undated (Box 198, Folder 23)
    - "The Church School’s Predicament and Place", undated (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - "Clearing the Way," W.R. White, undated (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - "The Coming Day of the Lord," W.R. White, undated (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - "Common Problems", undated (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Completed Articles by Dr. White (1 of 6), undated (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Completed Articles by Dr. White (2 of 6), undated (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Completed Articles by Dr. White (3 of 6), undated (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Completed Articles by Dr. White (4 of 6), undated (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Completed Articles by Dr. White (5 of 6), undated (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Completed Articles by Dr. White (6 of 6), undated (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - “Conflict with Authority” and “Hope for the Future”, undated (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - "Confusing, Catchy, Clichés," W.R. White, undated (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - "Congratulations Bishop College", undated (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - "The Critical Status of Christian Education in Today’s World", undated (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - "Dangerous Change Jeremiah 2:11, 13", undated (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - "The Deeper Meaning of Thanksgiving", undated (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - "The Deeper Reason for Christian Education", undated (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - "Dental Caries" by Bernhard Gottlieb, 1947 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - "Destroyers or Builders of an Enduring Society" Little Pack (Gambling), undated (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - "Differing without Dividing", 1969 (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - "The Dilemma of Christian Education", undated (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - "Does the Community Have Rights," W.R. White (1 of 2), undated (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - "Does the Community Have Rights," W.R. White (2 of 2), undated (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - Dr.’s Book Rough Copies, undated (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - "The Doctrine of Sin" by W.E. Cook Doctorate of Divinity (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - "The Doctrine of Sin" by W.E. Cook Doctorate of Divinity (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Drafts and Manuscripts (1 of 7), undated (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Drafts and Manuscripts (2 of 7), undated (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Drafts and Manuscripts (3 of 7), undated (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Drafts and Manuscripts (4 of 7), undated (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Drafts and Manuscripts (5 of 7), undated (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Drafts and Manuscripts (6 of 7), undated (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Drafts and Manuscripts (7 of 7), undated (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - "Education and Social Responsibility", undated (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - "Education at the Cross-Roads", undated (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - "The Education Philosophy of William R. White", undated (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - "Eschatology" (1 of 2), undated (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - "Eschatology" (2 of 2), undated (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - "The Evidence of Conversion Experience" (1 of 4), undated (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - "The Evidence of Conversion Experience" (2 of 4), undated (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - "The Evidence of Conversion Experience" (3 of 4), undated (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - "The Evidence of Conversion Experience" (4 of 4), undated (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - "Evolution and Anthropology", undated (Box 200, Folder 20)
    - "Exponents of Excellence" Address given May 5, 1964 at Oklahoma Baptist University, 1964 May 5 (Box 200, Folder 21)
    - "Exposition of First Peter" (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - "Exposition of First Peter" (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - "Fruitful Teaching for Adults", undated (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - "Frustration and Fulfillment," Baccalaureate Address (1 of 2), 1965 May (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - "Frustration and Fulfillment," Baccalaureate Address (2 of 2), 1965 May (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Dr. George W. Truett, undated (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - "The Geography of Christianity," W.R. White, undated (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - "Good Citizenship: Through Respect for the Dignity and Worth of the Individual", undated (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - “Gospel of Salvation” and “Regeneration”, undated (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - H.L. Hunt-Book: Alpaca(1 of 6), 1960 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - H.L. Hunt-Book: Alpaca(2 of 6), 1960 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - H.L. Hunt-Book: Alpaca (3 of 6), 1960 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - H.L. Hunt-Book: Alpaca (4 of 4), 1960 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - H.L. Hunt-Book: Alpaca (5 of 6), 1960 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - H.L. Hunt-Book: Alpaca (6 of 6), 1960 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - "Have They Died in Vain? or Do We Live in Vain?", undated (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - "How I Prepare My Sermons", undated (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Dr. Hutcherson’s: "Practical Approach to Church Finance" (1 of 2), undated (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Dr. Hutcherson’s: "Practical Approach to Church Finance" (2 of 2), undated (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - "Is Masonry a Church?", undated (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - "Indirect and Direct Evangelism," W.R. White, undated (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - "Individual Fulfillment", 1964 (Box 201, Folder 21)
    - "The Impact of Our Christian Heritage," W.R. White, undated (Box 201, Folder 22)
    - "The Irreducible Minimum" by W.R. White, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 23)
    - Jack Byrom-Inaugural Address San Marcos Academy, undated (Box 201, Folder 24)
    - "Journey Into Light", undated (Box 201, Folder 25)
    - “Let the Silent Majority Speak,” Published in Tribune Herald, 1969 November 9 (Box 201, Folder 26)
    - "Let Us All Define and Decide Together", undated (Box 201, Folder 27)
    - "Let’s Return to Content", 1965 March (Box 201, Folder 28)
    - "Life First and Last", undated (Box 201, Folder 29)
    - Literary Productions from White (1 of 4), undated (Box 201, Folder 30)
    - Literary Productions from White (2 of 4), undated (Box 201, Folder 31)
    - Literary Productions from White (3 of 4), undated (Box 201, Folder 32)
    - Literary Productions from White (4 of 4), undated (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Lubbock Evangelism Conference Messages, 1965 February 22 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - "Manifestation," Speech (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - "Manifestation," Speech (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - "Manifesto of Faith," Evaluations, etc. (1 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - "Manifesto of Faith," Evaluations, etc. (2 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - "Manifesto of Faith," Evaluations, etc. (3 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts, Radio Programs, 1950 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Manuscripts, 1951 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Marriage, undated (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Masonic Philosophy of Education, undated (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - "Masonry and Religion" sent to Masonic Magazine, 1969 January (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - "Masonry in the Scheme of Things", undated (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - "Maturing as a Baptist", undated (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Message Delivered at Mercer’s Gap, undated (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - "The Mission of the Christian Business Man" (1 of 2), undated (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - "The Mission of the Christian Business Man" (2 of 2), undated (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - "Moral Education in Public Schools", undated (Box 202, Folder 18)
    - "My Country," W.R. White Delivered to Lions Club-Ozona, Texas, undated (Box 202, Folder 19)
    - "My Work at Baylor", 1965 March 29 (Box 202, Folder 20)
    - "National Righteousness" by White, 1936 August 12-16 (Box 202, Folder 21)
    - Notes and Drafts, undated (Box 202, Folder 22)
    - “One Nation Under God,” Howard Payne College, 1967 May (Box 202, Folder 23)
    - "Paisano’s Powerful Preaching", undated (Box 202, Folder 24)
    - Pastors’ Digest, 1961 (Box 202, Folder 25)
    - "Perils and Promises", undated (Box 202, Folder 26)
    - "Pernicious Perils of the Day", undated (Box 202, Folder 27)
    - Pettengill Articles, 1947-1948 (Box 202, Folder 28)
    - "Pleasantly Pleasing Paisano," W.R. White, undated (Box 202, Folder 29)
    - "Philippines" (1 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 202, Folder 30)
    - "Philippines" (2 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - "Philippines" (3 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - "Philippines" (4 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - "The Position of College Administrators", undated (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - "Powerful Paisano", undated (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - "Preparation for the Future," W.R. White, undated (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - "Providential Kidnapping," W.R. White, undated (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - "The Pursuit of Complete Truth", undated (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - "Puzzled and Concerned", 1968 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - "The Question of Relevance", 1965 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - "The Relevancy of B.H. Carroll for Our Day," (Founder’s Day, Southwestern Seminary), undated (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - "The Relevancy of B.H. Carroll for Our Day", undated (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - "Religion and Thinking", undated (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - "Religion and Thinking", 1961 (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - "Religion and Thinking," by White, undated (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Review of “My Fiftieth Birthday as a Christian” by Dr. Jacob Gartenhaus, undated (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - "The Revolt Against Authority," Sent to Baptist Review Oct. 1969, 1969 October (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - "Righteousness Exalteth a Nation Proverbs 14:34," W.R. White, undated (Box 203, Folder 18)
    - "Righteousness Exalteth a Nation," by White, undated (Box 203, Folder 19)
    - Rough Draft of Dr.’s Book (1 of 5), undated (Box 203, Folder 20)
    - Rough Draft of Dr.'s Book (2 of 5), undated (Box 203, Folder 21)
    - Rough Draft of Dr.'s Book (3 of 5), undated (Box 203, Folder 22)
    - Rough Draft of Dr.'s Book (4 of 5), undated (Box 203, Folder 23)
    - Rough Draft of Dr.'s Book (5 of 5), undated (Box 203, Folder 24)
    - Scout Speech, undated (Box 203, Folder 25)
    - Separation and Cooperation or Isolation Sermons, undated (Box 203, Folder 26)
    - Sermons (1 of 2), undated (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Sermons (2 of 2), undated (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Sermons and Speeches by White (1 of 4), undated (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Sermons and Speeches by White (2 of 4), undated (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Sermons and Speeches by White (3 of 4), undated (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Sermons and Speeches by White (4 of 4), undated (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Sermons by White (1 of 5), 1946-1965 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Sermons by White (2 of 5), 1946-1965 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Sermons by White (3 of 5), 1946-1965 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Sermons by White (4 of 5), 1946-1965 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Sermons by White (5 of 5), 1946-1965 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Sermons of Dr. W.R. White, undated (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Sermons Prepared in Oklahoma City (1 of 5), 1938-1940 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Sermons Prepared in Oklahoma City (2 of 5), 1938-1940 (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Sermons Prepared in Oklahoma City (3 of 5), 1938-1940 (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Sermons Prepared in Oklahoma City (4 of 5), 1938-1940 (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Sermons Prepared in Oklahoma City (5 of 5), 1938-1940 (Box 204, Folder 17)
    - Sermons Put in Sermon Book (1 of 3), undated (Box 204, Folder 18)
    - Sermons Put in Sermon Book (2 of 3), undated (Box 204, Folder 19)
    - Sermons Put in Sermon Book (3 of 3), undated (Box 204, Folder 20)
    - Sermons to Go in Book List of Titles (1 of 2), undated (Box 204, Folder 21)
    - Sermons to Go in Book List of Titles (2 of 2), undated (Box 204, Folder 22)
    - "Shall We Be Unionists, Isolationists, or Separationist?", undated (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - "The Sins of the Saved" (1 of 3), undated (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - "The Sins of the Saved" (2 of 3), undated (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - "The Sins of the Saved" (3 of 3), undated (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Speeches (1 of 3), 1948 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Speeches (2 of 3), 1948 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Speeches (3 of 3), 1948 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Speeches-Dr. White, 1950-1951 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Speeches-Mixed (1 of 2), 1961-1971 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Speeches-Mixed (2 of 2), 1961-1971 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Speech on Christian Education-Southern Baptist Convention (1 of 3), 1969 June (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Speech on Christian Education-S.B.C. (2 of 3), 1969 June (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Speech on Christian Education-S.B.C. (3 of 3), 1969 June (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Speech to Red Cross of Constantine, 1970 June 6 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - "Some Assumptions Basic to Christian Education", undated (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - "Some Dynamic Spiritual Forces at Baylor", undated (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - "Some Observations on Academic Freedom and Responsibility", undated (Box 205, Folder 17)
    - "Some Serious Observations on 'Tongues'", undated (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - "Southern Baptist at the Crossroads", undated (Box 205, Folder 19)
    - "Southern Baptists at the Cross Roads", undated (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - "Southern Baptists Functioning in High", undated (Box 205, Folder 21)
    - "Southern Baptists on Church Unity", undated (Box 205, Folder 22)
    - "Sovereignty of God", undated (Box 205, Folder 23)
    - The Survey Bulletin, 1960-1961 (Box 205, Folder 24)
    - "There Is a Difference. Separation and Cooperation Or Isolation" (1 of 2), undated (Box 205, Folder 25)
    - "There Is a Difference, Separation and Cooperation Or Isolation" (2 of 2), undated (Box 205, Folder 26)
    - "They Live Abundantly", undated (Box 205, Folder 27)
    - "The Third W.B. Jack Ball Lecture" by White Bound Volume, 1972 September 26 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - "This Is the Man", 1959 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - "Those Incomparable Missionaries" (1 of 2), undated (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - "Those Incomparable Missionaries" (2 of 2), undated (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - "Those Peculiar Baptists", undated (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - "Titov Finds No God", undated (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - "To Drink Or Not to Drink", 1965 April 22 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - "Trends in the Orient", undated (Box 206, Folder 8)